CHAIN. Critical-component sourcing in a polycrisis world.
When a Taiwan Strait or Suez disruption hits, which Marine programs are exposed?
Thirty named nodes — TSMC, ASML, rare-earth mines, primes, and USMC end-items.
Sixty days of synthetic disruption events stream in — typhoons, cyber, export controls.
A multi-step LLM agent analyzes the disrupted network — structured JSON.
Then a Kamiwaza-deployed model writes a Critical-Component Risk Brief for PEO Land Systems.
Exposed programs. Substitute suppliers. Lead-time impact. Mitigation playbook.
Three pre-baked scenarios — Taiwan Strait, Suez compound, rare-earth freeze.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire — air-gapped, IL5/IL6 ready.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.