CADENCE. Adaptive PME tutor for every Marine.
PME training problem: one-size-fits-all is not working at the artifact level.
Three demo courses. Three Marines. One personalized study plan each.
Marine logs in. CADENCE reads their docx submission and last 10 forum posts.
Three-stage agent. Read. Analyze. Plan.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model drafts the one-page Adaptive Study Plan.
Knowledge gaps. Doctrine to review. Three tailored study questions.
Seven-day learning targets. Daily action. Rubric-aligned writing tips.
Privacy Act of 1974 and DoDI 1322.35. NAVMC 3500 T&R cited. SHA-256 chained. Data stays in the SCIF.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. From Context to Action. Deploy in hours.