STOCKROOM. AI-augmented inventory control management for the supply NCO.
LOGCOM use case: 5,000 items, disconnected Excel docs, no relational view.
Five thousand items in scope. Filter by location, category, custodian.
Top metrics surface inventory-overdue and NMC-impacting counts immediately.
Type a question in plain English. The AI engine parses it into a JSON filter spec.
Visible parsed spec — no SQL, no opaque magic. Then it runs against the table.
The hero model drafts a Readiness and Lateral Transfer Brief.
BLUF, overdue counts, NMC shortages, sensitive-item flags, three actions.
Three clicks: pick a scenario, surface the gaps, copy actions to the standup.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire. IL5 / IL6 ready.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.