DRONE-DOMINANCE. Full UAS encounter lifecycle on a single screen.
UAS-vs-FOB. The problem Marines added to MDM 2026 themselves.
Friendly fleet — visual quantification of own platforms. 39 drones across 5 make/models.
Hostile contact. Three sensor modalities side by side — RF, thermal IR, visual EO.
Three multimodal calls in one workflow. Bayesian product fuses them — math shown, not hidden.
Operator switches to the swarm scenario. Pipeline reruns end-to-end.
Engagement decision: graded ROE ladder. Authority required is shown per option.
Hero model writes the UAS Encounter Brief. 10 USC 130i, JP 3-01, JCO-CUAS — only authorized references.
Egocentric AAR. Helmet-cam still plus operator decision, scored against doctrine.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL. Same code. CUAS decisions stay in the SCIF.
IL5 / IL6 ready. ReBAC. Air-gapped. Zero data movement.
DRONE-DOMINANCE. Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Powered by Kamiwaza.