GUARDRAIL. Trusted Marine workspace — four governance layers, one verifiable chain.
CUI auto-tagging + ABAC + browser-AI gov + hash-chained audit — all in one shell.
Active persona: Pvt Joe Mason, SECRET clearance. Watch what he can see.
Layer 1 — per-paragraph CUI marking under DoDM 5200.01 Vol 2.
Switch persona to Capt Doe (TS-SCI). ABAC re-renders the same document.
Now the contractor — Quinn Park. Privacy-Act and ITAR paragraphs disappear.
Open the intel summary. SECRET//NOFORN paragraphs are redacted by clearance.
Layer 3 — browser-AI gov. Stream the live intercept feed.
Comet, manus.im, Skyvern — BLOCKED at the workspace boundary.
Ask the workspace AI. RAG over only the paragraphs ABAC authorizes.
Layer 4 — one SHA-256 chain across CUI marks, ABAC redactions, browser blocks, AI queries.
Hero call: a Workspace Governance Posture Brief — cache-first, ready before the click.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — the whole workspace stays inside the SCIF.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.