STORM-SHIFT. Polycrisis readiness for USMC installations.
The polycrisis era is here — storms cascade into supply, inventory, and fire.
Operator picks installation, storm scenario, optional co-event.
Five datasets: NASA Earthdata, FIRMS, NFIP, FEMA Climate-SC, CA Logistics.
Six projection agents fan out in parallel — flood, supply, inventory, consumption, impact, fire.
Sankey diagram renders the cascade chain — storm to flood to supply to inventory red.
72-hour cascade timeline · polycrisis multiplier surfaces non-linear compounding.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model writes the Polycrisis Readiness Brief.
Storm models stay in your enclave. No cloud egress. Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.