MARLIN. Maritime Anomaly and Risk Intelligence Layer.
LOGCOM contested logistics: dark vessels and gray-zone rendezvous in the second island chain.
Ten vessel tracks. One thousand AIS pings. One hundred-event timeline replaying live.
Three anomalies surface automatically: AIS gap, denied-area loiter, and a midnight rendezvous.
We click the flagged tanker. A Kamiwaza-deployed model reads the track, neighbors, and denied areas.
A three-paragraph intel narrative streams in, citing specific timestamps and lat lon coordinates.
Pattern of life. Anomaly analysis. A time-bounded recommendation for the watch officer.
A second JSON-mode call returns structured indicators ready for tipping and cueing.
Running on a Kamiwaza-deployed model behind KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL. Air-gapped, IL5/IL6 ready.
One hundred percent data containment. Nothing leaves your accredited environment.
MARLIN. Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.