OMNI-AGENT. Your Marines have 53 AI tools - this is the one that picks the right one.
Cross-domain decisions: blood readiness is a weather problem is a sustainment problem.
Fourteen sibling apps wired as governed tools - the Kamiwaza Tool Garden.
VITALS, WEATHERVANE, MERIDIAN, CONTESTED-LOG, REORDER, CUAS-DETECT, OMNI...
One operator query. The agent decomposes and fires three tools in sequence.
VITALS reports blood readiness. WEATHERVANE confirms the typhoon window. MERIDIAN scores nodes.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model fuses every result into one OPORD-style brief.
Every tool invocation is SHA-256 hash-chain audited for SJA forensics.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL - the orchestration layer stays inside your enclave too.
OMNI-AGENT - Kamiwaza unifies your AI fleet. Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack.