EMBODIED. Egocentric multimodal Marine training simulator.
LOGCOM training modernization: instructor-to-trainee ratio is the bottleneck.
Eight egocentric scenarios — doorway, checkpoint, casualty, IED, night perimeter.
Each scenario is anchored to a doctrine reference — MCWP, MCRP, TM. No invention.
Trainee types their action. Multimodal coach reads the frame plus the response.
Vision-capable model classifies the action against doctrine. Structured JSON.
Score, doctrine cite, simulated consequence, coaching feedback — in one shot.
After-action across attempts — a one-page Egocentric Decision Brief.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — same code, trainee video stays inside the wire.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.