HUB. Multimodal CONUS movement planner for Marine logistics.
LOGCOM problem set: contested logistics, supply chain, expeditionary ops.
Marine planners need one pane to compare road, rail, waterway, and air to a POE.
BTS NTAD: 30 hubs, 47 typed multimodal edges, 10 USMC end-items.
Pick origin, POE, and end-item — Albany to Beaumont with an M1A1 Abrams.
A multi-step AI engine fuses per-mode capacity, clearance, and weight limits.
Three-click answer: recommended mode, named bottleneck, alternate corridors.
Bottleneck named — I-10 Lake Charles bridge weight class — M1A1 NO-GO without permit.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire — air-gapped, IL5 ready.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.