CUAS-DETECT. Counter-UAS RF detection for Marine installation force protection.
LOGCOM Installation Incident Response. The OOD has thirty seconds to call it.
Six sample spectrograms — DJI Mavic, Parrot Anafi, fixed-wing, hobbyist quad, swarm, ambient.
Stage 1: heuristic features. Numpy on the spectrogram — peak bins, hop period, modulation hint.
Stage 2: multimodal AI engine ingests the spectrogram. Structured CUAS JSON.
Class, controller signature, intent, range, recommended COA, EOC callout.
Operator picks the swarm capture. Pipeline reruns end-to-end.
Stage 3: hero model writes the CUAS Engagement Recommendation.
BLUF, contact ID, threat assessment, ROE-graded options, recommended COA.
Engagement options graded passive, non-kinetic, kinetic — each with required authority.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — same code, now on the Inference Mesh.
IL5 / IL6 ready. ReBAC. Air-gapped. Zero data movement.
CUAS-DETECT. Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Powered by Kamiwaza.