TRACE. Class one through nine sustainment estimates in seconds.
LOGCOM use case: a logistics estimate informed by doctrine and consumption rates.
Inputs: unit type, personnel, days, climate, opscale.
Synthetic GCSS-MC depots and MCWP four-eleven planning rates load locally - no data movement.
A two-step agentic pipeline produces the full Class one through nine estimate.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model drafts a one-page Sustainment Estimate Brief.
Daily lbs-equivalent stacked across all nine classes. Sources per class.
Top depots per class - on-hand quantity and percent of window covered.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.