MARINE-MEDIC. Joint Class VIII and casualty-flow decision support.
Casualty in 30 minutes. Supply chain in 30 hours. We close the loop on both.
TCCC and JTS triage, hub-spoke supply check, GCSS-MC requisition, all in one chain.
One regional med depot at Apra. Twelve distributed Marine units across WestPac.
Inject the scenario: HE blast MASCAL on a 13th MEU FRSS, twenty-two WIA inbound.
Six-stage agent chain runs: triage cards stream per WIA in JSON-mode.
Class VIII demand projects time-phased over 1, 6, 12, 24 hours.
Hub-spoke check finds the gap. Auto-requisition pops in GCSS-MC format.
A Kamiwaza-deployed hero model writes the Medical Sustainment Action Brief.
Casualty data stays in IL5 enclave. Hash-chained audit, HIPAA and NDAA flavored.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.