GUARDIAN. Stop browser AI from acting on internal LOGCOM apps.
LOGCOM use case: browser-based agent governance — protect CUI from Comet, manus.im, and the rest.
Eight active policies in the sidebar. Every event is screened against them.
Synthetic browser intercepts stream into the GUARDIAN middleware — no data movement.
Per-event chat_json policy decision — agent class, confidence, signals, action.
Color-coded decisions: ALLOW · BLOCK · CHALLENGE_HUMAN · REDACT_PII.
Every decision is appended to a SHA-256 hash-chained audit log.
Hero call: a posture brief — BLUF, top exfil vectors, recommended tightening.
Cache-first. The brief is ready before the operator clicks. Three scenarios pre-staged.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code routes inside your accredited boundary.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.