QUEUE. Depot Maintenance Throughput Optimizer.
LOGCOM use case: AI-driven scheduling for induction sequencing, workforce, and parts.
Three depots: MCLB Albany, Barstow, Blount Island Command.
Eighty end items ingested from a GCSS-MC stand-in. No data movement.
Greedy priority-weighted scheduler emits a 30-day Plotly Gantt across 3 depots.
Hero AI layer analyzes the schedule. Structured JSON, then narrative brief.
Bottleneck named. Parts cascading effects. Top-5 actions for next 30 days.
Tune workforce or parts release on the sidebar — the Gantt re-renders live.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs against an on-prem model.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Air-gapped, IL5/IL6 ready.