PREDICT-MAINT. Closed-loop predictive maintenance — sensor to shelf in five stages.
The Marine reading the failure 30 days late is the Marine who loses the truck mid-mission.
PREDICT-MAINT closes that loop before the gap opens.
Five datasets fused: CWRU, NASA CMAPSS, Azure PdM, GCSS-MC, ICM workbook. No data movement.
Operator clicks the MTVR-2491 bearing — the 5-stage chain fires.
Sensor classifier — 30-day forecast — auto-reorder — depot reslot — SHA-256 ledger.
Spectrogram with BPFO/BPFI/BSF/FTF lines — RandomForest calls the fault.
Holt-Winters projects the spike. Auto-reorder card emits structured JSON.
Depot Gantt reslots the asset at MCLB Albany. SHA-256 ledger signs the row.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire — air-gapped, IL5/IL6 ready.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.