STRIDER. Tells autonomous Marines what they are rolling onto.
Force Design 2030 puts Marines in places maps do not reach.
LOGCOM fields the autonomous tow tractor at MDMC Albany today, ALPV tomorrow.
Forward rover snaps a frame. GOOSE off-road imagery, never leaves the wire.
Fifty gigabytes of labelled terrain, on-prem.
Kamiwaza-deployed vision call: terrain frame becomes structured JSON.
Soft sand. Very-soft firmness. No water crossing.
Reasoner cross-references fording depth and ground clearance per vehicle.
Green, amber, red. Binding constraint named in plain English.
ALPV caution. JLTV caution. ATT-EV NO-GO -- 6.5 inch clearance bogs in soft sand.
Convoy commander has the answer in four seconds.
Audit trail: full JSON every call. Operator can replay any decision.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL. Same code hits on-prem vLLM. 100% data containment.
IL5 / IL6 ready. STIG-hardened. Inference Mesh handles the routing.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.