SPECTRA. Raw I/Q in, threat picture out.
Marine FOB Spectrum Awareness — what is in my bubble, is any of it not ours?
Six synthetic 1-second I/Q captures. NIST SigMF schema.
STFT renders the spectrogram. SigMF header on the right.
Multimodal model ingests the spectrogram plus the SigMF header.
Strict JSON: modulation, protocol, anomaly flag, confidence.
Hero model drafts a SIPR-format Spectrum Awareness Brief.
BLUF, header, top emitters, anomalies, recommended actions.
Three clicks: pick a capture, classify, draft the brief.
Unauthorized-band emitter. Cached brief loads instantly.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — same code, now on the Inference Mesh.
IL5 / IL6 ready. ReBAC. Air-gapped. Zero data movement.
SPECTRA. Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Powered by Kamiwaza.