VITALS. Joint blood-logistics decision support for DHA RESCUE.
USINDOPACOM Distributed Maritime Operations — one depot, twelve spokes.
Predicting which spoke fails first when the hub gets constrained.
Twelve distributed Marine units stream onto the hub-and-spoke map.
Constrain the hub: airlift loss, typhoon CPA inside 48 hours.
Spokes turn red one-by-one as the cascading-failure simulation runs.
A multi-step LLM agent scores all 12 spokes — strict JSON output.
Then a Kamiwaza-deployed hero model drafts the Commander's Decision Brief.
BLUF, top-3 spoke nodes at risk, secondary-effect cascades. One page.
Mitigation actions cite approved buy-on-market vendors by id.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.