OPTIK — On-Prem Tactical Image Knowledge.
MARADMIN 131/26: anticipate equipment failure, improve readiness.
A motor-pool Marine vs. 3,400 pages of Technical Manual.
30 synthetic TM snippets indexed at startup — text-embedding-3-small.
Swappable to your real GCSS-MC corpus on a Kamiwaza DDE volume.
Drag-drop a field photo.
Single Kamiwaza-deployed multimodal call. Structured-JSON detection schema.
Vision -> bounding boxes -> RAG over TM snippets.
Senior-Sergeant-tone brief with TM number, section, and NSNs.
Three clicks. Identify. Read brief. Print parts list.
JSON ready to push to GCSS-MC. E-5 answers in 4 seconds.
Kamiwaza-deployed inference today. OpenAI fallback when KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL unset — zero code change.
Qwen2-VL or LLaVA on vLLM Inference Mesh. IL5/IL6 ready.
OPTIK — Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.