SCHOOLHOUSE. Marine schoolhouse-in-a-box.
PME today is three disconnected systems and a tired NCO. We fold them into one.
Four datasets. Three use cases. One on-prem stack. Three role-aware views.
Switch to the student view — start with an egocentric tactical drill.
Multimodal coach reads the helmet-cam frame plus the Marine's typed action.
Switch drill — Visual ID. Drop a foreign platform image.
Vision-language analyst writes the numbered reasoning. SENTINEL pattern.
Switch drill — Written assignment. Logistics principles paper.
chat_json grades each rubric criterion. 0-5 score plus narrative feedback.
Switch role — Instructor. Same data, reshaped — cohort heatmap appears.
Cache-first Schoolhouse Intelligence Brief. Anchored to NAVMC 3500.58.
Switch role — School CO. Same brief reshapes to a schoolhouse health dashboard.
Audit chain — every drill, every brief, SHA-256 chained. Privacy Act governed, not FERPA.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — PME data stays inside the SCIF.
Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.