CORSAIR. Maritime risk forecasts for contested logistics.
Every MEU PMC routes through three of the top five piracy basins.
NGA ASAM gives you yesterday. CORSAIR gives you the next 30 days.
60 by 60 KDE grid. Recency weighted. Seasonality corrected.
An LLM agent ingests the top five hotspots and recent attack narratives.
It drafts a SIPR-format Maritime Intel Summary and structured indicator board.
Three clicks: theater, generate, drilldown.
Drill into a hotspot — the three real incidents that produced the forecast appear.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL — same code, now on-prem via the Inference Mesh.
IL5 / IL6 ready. ReBAC. Zero data movement.
CORSAIR. Built on the Kamiwaza Stack. Powered by Kamiwaza.