CHORUS. Public Affairs trainees rehearse five audiences before they press send.
LOGCOM use case: AI-Enabled Public Affairs Training and Audience Simulation.
Fifteen synthetic personas across domestic media, host-nation, and adversary IO.
Pick a scenario. A drone strike near a host-nation village. The clock is running.
A trainee drafts the release. CHORUS runs it past five personas in parallel.
Each persona returns structured JSON: trust delta, narrative risk, predicted action.
Five color-coded persona cards. Aggregate trust delta and counter-message risk.
A Kamiwaza-deployed hero model writes a one-page Message Effectiveness Brief.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire. No data movement.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Train PA officers in hours, not months.