MERIDIAN. Climate-resilience watch over MARFORPAC supply lines.
LOGCOM problem set: contested logistics, supply chain, expeditionary ops.
Twelve critical nodes — Guam to Okinawa to CNMI to the Philippines.
Thirty NOAA, JTWC, FEMA, and G-4 reports stream in — no data movement.
A multi-step LLM agent scores all twelve nodes — structured JSON.
Then a Kamiwaza-deployed model drafts a USMC OPORD-style five-paragraph brief.
Top-3 named threats. Recommended COA per CCDR. One page.
Inject a new incident — re-rank the chain in seconds.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.