REORDER. Class IX demand forecasting for contested logistics.
LOGCOM use case: predict Class IX consumption for a deployed MAGTF.
OPTEMPO, environment, and historical maintenance drive the forecast.
Ninety days of GCSS-MC work orders stream in. No data movement.
A Holt-Winters forecaster projects each NSN thirty, sixty, ninety days out.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model judges each top-N NSN — RED, AMBER, GREEN — with a pre-position action.
Sortable risk table. Pre-position by depot and date. One sustainment brief.
Forward nodes plus recommended pre-position flows on the map.
Set KAMIWAZA_BASE_URL and the same code runs inside the wire.
Powered by the Kamiwaza Stack. Deploy in hours, not months.