LEARN. Cognitive-development analytics for USMC schoolhouses.
LOGCOM use case: Learning Intelligence Dashboard. Are Marines actually learning?
Eighteen students. Six assignments. Two hundred forum posts. One question.
Synthetic Moodle export streams in. No data movement.
A three-stage agent scores every student against the USMC competency rubric, anchored to NAVMC 3500.18 Infantry T&R.
A Kamiwaza-deployed model drafts the Instructors Competency Brief, cited to NAVMC 3500.18.
Three-click drill-down: heatmap to student to remediation. Sergeants Course at SNCO Academy is distinct from the Squad Leader Course at SOI.
Class-level competency map. Top performers. Intervention list.
Every assessment SHA-256 chained. Privacy Act of 1974 and DoDI 1322.35 governed. SJA, IG, TECOM can replay.
Powered by Kamiwaza. Privacy Act 1974 and DoDI 1322.35 governed. IL5 ready. Deploy in hours.